so today's look is called Queen at the
red carpet featuring my fabulous
lipstick legendary Queen so darlings I'm
going to start off by using my miracle
working magic cream
let's I'm going to use my magic I rescue
cream so darlings now I'm going to apply
my magic foundation and I'm going to mix
it with my Hollywood of flawless filter
so I'm applying this with my Hollywood
complexion brush and this is just a
fantastic brush it really gets the
foundational super quick and easy the
Hollywood flawless filter just really
does give you the most beautiful skin
and makes everyone look more youthful
and younger so done is now I'm going to
use my retouch of retouches fantastic
for concealing blemishes so we're just
gonna pop on number 5
I'm gonna take my lovely Hollywood brush
it's fantastic I love it it's so good
nimble to use I'm now going to use my
mini miracle I want this has a peptide
serum on one side and then on the other
side we've got this wonderful thing it's
a real light reflector for FBI
now I'm going to apply a wet carpet
essential this is my airbrush a flawless
finish of powder and it really really is
the best powder in the world this powder
does actually makes you look airbrushed
it's amazing on the red carpet we're
live TV everything this is your best
friend it is a real throw this I'm using
number two people every news face but I
like to use a slightly lighter powder
underneath the eyes
[Music]
imma start off by doing
nimmi's brows with my brow lift
[Music]
this is perfect brow and you just pop it
through it's so easy to use I mean
literally anyone could use this and it
just brushes up a hesitancy the hairs
and perfect brows is the most amazing
dark colors and new color that we've
just creators eyelash colors are so
important can hold like 10 seconds and
you can always repeat if you need more
now I'm going to use an behave this is a
really beautiful soft bronze color which
I just adore I'm just going to scribble
it on the eyelid like this what I love
about this is you get maximum effect for
very little effort this is the product
for people who don't have to do makeup
it's just heaven now cream eyeshadow
this cream eyeshadow is fabulous eyes to
mesmerize and I take my smudger brush
and dipping it into this divine shade
this bronzy gold it just looks great on
all skin tones I'm gonna go into the
inner corner here and I'm just gonna do
a little you time not just kind of opens
it up keeping it close to the lash line
[Music]
welcome call eyeliner and darshan outer
corner and then go right in along the
lash line and then you go in a little
bit along the lash line but not all the
way and what's brought us about this
eyeliner is that it lasts for up to 12
hours I'm using my full fat lashes
mascara and it's fabulous because it
adds a volume length and drama all in
one's gone I'm using my mascara
vertically if I actually had this
tapered to be able to do the bottom
lashes individually now I'm gonna use my
Hollywood comfortable wand and this is
fantastic for just sculpting and shaping
the face and I'm going to use my
Hollywood complexion brush I'm just
literally in circular movements just
gonna blend this in beautifully it's
just miraculous what this does it really
can sculpt the face I'm finally but the
other comes doing the nose I like to
take the other tip my Hollywood
collection brush because it sort of
smoothes be used down the nose and
around the nose so now I'm going to use
my film stop on some glow I'm gonna take
my sculpting brush and dipping it into
the highlight shade this is a beautiful
dreamy Golden Sun set Hugh and this is
something I've used a lot it's it my
blending brush into the darker film-star
bronze & Glow I just
[Music]
now I've got walk of shame little I know
it suits a lot of lots of skin tones
sort of rose petal in heaven I adore it
lies cuz not gonna give you some of the
perfect pout but also they keep the
lipstick from moving
so now darlings legendary Queen and
lipstick that I just think it's the
mister buying color it is a soft neutral
wine this is also a fabulous color for
all sorts of skin tones and eye colors
you could pretty much put on anyone last
but not least I'm going to use my cheek
to cheek blusher in climax and I'm going
to swish and pop this is such a pretty
peachy bronze
I think divine I always finish off every
look by spraying the magic way in using
cents a dream don't forget to give
yourself the gorgeous scent halo of the
trail so there you have it the queen of
the red carpet right here
[Music]